const STORE = [
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the best aerosolized bronchodilator for a patient with an acute asthma attack?",
      options: [
        "albuterol (proventil)", 
        "ipratropium bromide (Atrovent)", 
        "cromolyn sodium (Intal)", 
        "budesonide/formoterol (Symbicort)"
      ],
      answer: "albuterol (proventil)"
    },

    {
      question: "Which of the following drugs is the most appropriate to sedate a 30-year-old patient with status asthmaticus and hypotension who is receiving mechanical ventilation?",
      options: [
        "vecuronium bromide (Norcuron)", 
        "lorazepam (Ativan)", 
        "morphine sulfate", 
        "oxycodone HCL (oxycotin)"
      ],
      answer: "lorazepam (Ativan)"
    },

    {
      question: "A respiratory therapist is performing spirometry on a patient with pulmonary fibrosis. Which of the following devices would possibly be damaged by this procedure?",
      options: [
        "wrights respirometer", 
        "peak flowmeter", 
        "vortex shedding device", 
        "water seal spirometer"
      ],
      answer: "wrights respirometer"
    },

    {
      question: "A physiologic goal of CPAP in atelectasis is to increase:",
      options: [
        "tidal volume", 
        "functional residual capacity", 
        "inspiratory capacity", 
        "minute alveolar ventilation"
      ],
      answer: "functional residual capacity"
    },

    {
      question: "Which of the following is the best way to assess the effectiveness of external chest compressions?",
      options: [
        "observe the patient's chest excursion", 
        "check the patient nail bed color", 
        "palpate the patient's carotid pulse", 
        "obtaining an ABG"
      ],
      answer: "palpate the patient's carotid pulse"
    },

    {
      question: "Following endotracheal intubation of a patient in the ED, what of the following should the RT use to confirm proper tube placement?",
      options: [
        "galvanic analyzer", 
        "mass spectrometer", 
        "calorimetric capnometer", 
        "severinghaus electrode"
      ],
      answer: "calorimetric capnometer"
    },

    {
      question: "A spontaneously breathing adult patient is intubated with a 6.0 mm ID endotracheal tube. Which of the following would decrease the patient's work of breathing imposed by the ET tube?",
      options: [
        "CPAP", 
        "pressure support", 
        "flow-by", 
        "inspiratory pause"
      ],
      answer: "pressure support"
    },

    {
      question: "A patient's V/Q scan reveals normal ventilation with absent perfusion in the left lower lobe. These results suggest:",
      options: [
        "right to left shunt", 
        "pulmonary embolism", 
        "pneumonia", 
        "hemothorax"
      ],
      answer: "pulmonary embolism"
    },

    {
      question: "Which of the following most consistently delivers the highest water vapor content to a patient's airway?",
      options: [
        "jet nebulizer", 
        "bubble humidifier", 
        "heated wick humidifier", 
        "hea moisture exchanger"
      ],
      answer: "heated wick humidifier"
    },

    {
      question: "This is a deflation of the alveoli of the lung which results in reduced gas exchange (terminology)",
      options: [
        "atelectasis", 
        "pleural effusion", 
        "asthma", 
        "respiratory failure"
      ],
      answer: "atelectasis"
    },

    {
      question: "An acute respiratory syndrome seen in children and infants characterized by a barking cough (terminology)",
      options: [
        "cyanosis", 
        "croup", 
        "dyspnea", 
        "cystic fibrosis"
      ],
      answer: "croup"
    },

    {
      question: "An abnormal condition in which the skin turns a bluish color caused by decreased oxygen and increased carbon dioxide in the blood (terminology)",
      options: [
        "hyperpnea", 
        "cyanosis", 
        "dyspnea", 
        "empyema"
      ],
      answer: "cyanosis"
    },

    {
      question: "This medical apparatus is inserted through the mouth and trachea to establish an airway: (terminology)",
      options: [
        "IPPB", 
        "eustachian tube", 
        "Heimlich tube", 
        "endotracheal tube"
      ],
      answer: "endotracheal tube"
    },

    {
      question: 'The prefix in the word, "anoxia", means (terminology)',
      options: [
        "oxygen", 
        "with", 
        "without", 
        "air"
      ],
      answer: "without"
    },

    {
      question: "Abnormal respiratory sounds characterized by fine crackles: (terminology)",
      options: [
        "dyspnea", 
        "rhonchi", 
        "wheezing", 
        "rales"
      ],
      answer: "rales"
    }
];